NOCETTI FERREIRA KAIQUE



Personal

♠ Address

1500 Rua Durval Fonseca Jardim Europa 25963300 Teresópolis

Phone number 21982501701

Email kaiquenocetti07@gmail.com

Languages

English

Portuguese

••••

Interests

- Business
- Computing
- Knowledge
- Learn Node.JS

I have a long background in a software company and with that I have a lot of experience and evolution in the field in which I work. Thus benefiting the company, as well as my own professional development.

Project almost 100% https://ajfimoveis.com.br/

This is my main project, with which I got my first job. I have a lot of affection for him, after he evolves along with me. It started as a static real estate listing website. Today it is dynamic and with the registration of properties being done through a panel. This project is almost 100% because there are still some adjustments left, but it is the one that is closest to being finalized.

Work experience

IT Technical Assistant

Sep 2021 - Present

ITH2O TECNOLOGIA EM INFORMÁTICA LTDA, Teresópolis

- Supported staff with clerical tasks for well-maintained office administration.
- Completed work to agreed standards and specifications.

Identified office equipment malfunctions and scheduled maintenance activities with repair teams to restore functionality.

- Attended and captured meetings' minutes, utilising short-hand formats to record discussions and conclusions.
- Harnessed prioritisation, organisation and multi-tasking skills and tools in handling multiple tasks, amplifying productivity.
- Assessed and modified office procedures to improve organisation and accuracy.
- Expedited work completion by coordinating internal and external resources to fulfil organisational goals.
- Managed information on company databases for different organisational activities to track history and safeguard accurate information.

Sep 2023 - Jul 2023

Education and Qualifications

Business Jun 2021 - Present

FAEL - Faculdade Educacional da Lapa, Rio de Janeiro

Fullstack Developer

Sep 2021 - Sep 2022

Danki Code, Rio de Janeiro

Skills

WordPress

PHP	••••
HTML	••••
Excel	
CSS	••••
JavaScript	••••
Bootstrap	
Jquery	••••
React	
MySLQ	
Computer skills	••••
Sass	
Git - GitHub	
User Experience (UX)	
User Interface (UI)	••••
Lavarel	••••